<rubrics schemaversion="v2011"><rubric id="1" resource_code="E3B84118-B59F-4D0C-847A-CA9AEC8F29C8-81033" name="BD assignment 1" type="1" scoring_method="2" display_levels_in_des_order="False" state="0" visibility="0" uses_overall_score="True" has_manual_alignment="False" score_visible_to_assessed_users="True" enabled_feedback_copy="False" usage_restrictions="Competency,ePortfolio"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><criteria_groups><criteria_group name="Criteria" sort_order="1"><level_set><levels><level name="Not (or hardly) shown" sort_order="1" level_value="0.000000000" level_id="64528" /><level name="Insufficient" sort_order="2" level_value="4.000000000" level_id="64527" /><level name="Poor" sort_order="3" level_value="8.000000000" level_id="64526" /><level name="Sufficient" sort_order="4" level_value="12.000000000" level_id="64525" /><level name="Good" sort_order="5" level_value="16.000000000" level_id="64524" /><level name="Excellent" sort_order="6" level_value="20.000000000" level_id="66880" /></levels></level_set><criteria><criterion name="Framework selection" sort_order="1"><cells><cell level_id="64528" cell_value="0.000000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;(below sufficient)&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="64527" cell_value="4.000000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;The research document has one of the following problems. It contains errors or is incomplete. There is no systematic way of scoring the frameworks. The document is highly opiniated or biased.&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="64526" cell_value="8.000000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;(between sufficient and insufficient)&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="64525" cell_value="12.000000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;There is a well-written research document. Both generic criteria and criteria from the advanced track are used. Each framework has been scored in an systematic and understandable way. Decisions are justified. An overview shows the final scores. Referencing is done using APA or IEEE. All reasoning is comprehensive and logical.&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="64524" cell_value="16.000000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;(between sufficient and excellent)&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="66880" cell_value="20.000000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;There is a thorough, well-written research document with cover, TOC, introduction and conclusion. Each framework has been described. All criteria and its weight are described, including the reasoning behind it. The criteria of the advanced track are elaborated. Each framework has been scored in a systematic and repeatable way. Decisions are justified and backed by sources, using a consistent way of referencing using APA or IEEE. An overview shows the final scores in a clear way. All text is well-written, informative, consistent, comprehensive, clear and logical&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell></cells></criterion><criterion name="Prototyping" sort_order="2"><cells><cell level_id="64528" cell_value="0.000000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;(below insufficient)&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="64527" cell_value="4.000000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;The research document has one of the following problems. It contains errors or is incomplete. The reflection is not systematic. The conclusion is not logical or based mainly on opinions or bias.&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="64526" cell_value="8.000000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;(between sufficient and insufficient)&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="64525" cell_value="12.000000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;There is a research document for the prototyping phase. The document describes the prototyping phase and reflects on the use of both frameworks. The reflection is systematic, clear and logical and based on own experiences. The conclusion is clear and logical, and in line with the reflections.&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="64524" cell_value="16.000000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;(between sufficient and excellent)&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="66880" cell_value="20.000000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;There is a well-written research document for the prototyping phase. The document describes the prototyping phase and reflects on the use of both frameworks. The reflection is uniform for both frameworks, and based on own experiences. The reflection is systematic and uses the criteria from phase 1. A final conclusion has been drawn that is in line with the reflections. The conclusion does not introduce new information. All text is well-written, informative, consistent, comprehensive, clear and logical.&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell></cells></criterion></criteria></criteria_group></criteria_groups><overall_level_set><overall_levels><overall_level name="Not (or hardly)" sort_order="5" range_start_value="0.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level><overall_level name="Insufficient" sort_order="6" range_start_value="8.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level><overall_level name="Poor" sort_order="4" range_start_value="16.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level><overall_level name="Sufficient" sort_order="3" range_start_value="24.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level><overall_level name="Good" sort_order="1" range_start_value="32.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level><overall_level name="Outstanding" sort_order="2" range_start_value="40.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level></overall_levels></overall_level_set></rubric><rubric id="2" resource_code="E3B84118-B59F-4D0C-847A-CA9AEC8F29C8-99546" name="BD assignment 2" type="1" scoring_method="3" display_levels_in_des_order="False" state="0" visibility="0" uses_overall_score="True" has_manual_alignment="False" score_visible_to_assessed_users="True" enabled_feedback_copy="False" usage_restrictions="Competency,ePortfolio"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><criteria_groups><criteria_group name="Criteria" sort_order="1"><level_set><levels><level name="Bad" sort_order="1" level_id="66912" /><level name="Insufficient" sort_order="2" level_id="66907" /><level name="Poor" sort_order="3" level_id="66906" /><level name="Sufficient" sort_order="4" level_id="66905" /><level name="Good" sort_order="5" level_id="66904" /><level name="Excellent" sort_order="6" level_id="66913" /></levels></level_set><criteria><criterion name="Technical spec" sort_order="1"><cells><cell level_id="66912" cell_value="0.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="66907" cell_value="3.000000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;There is technical specification that does not clarify the important parts of the application. The Open API specification is incorrect or incomplete&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="66906" cell_value="6.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="66905" cell_value="9.000000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;There is a technical specification with a list of prioritized requirements. It gives a technical overview of the application, and describes the important components and parts that are harder to understand in detail. Technical choices are explained, including considered alternatives. The API specification covers all functionality and has useful, correct and complete descriptions. References are done in a consistent way using APA or IEEE. &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="66904" cell_value="12.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="66913" cell_value="15.000000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;There is a thorough and well-written technical specification. All parts are clear, comprehensive, correct, logical, useful, consistent, and complete. It contains the reason for this application and a list of prioritized requirements. It gives a technical overview of the application. All components are described in detail in a structured way. Technical choices are explained including considered alternatives. The link between the components is clear. Parts that are harder to understand are explained in more detail. Diagrams are included to enlighten the text. The API specification covers all endpoints. The specification has useful, correct and complete descriptions. It has example calls, with an example response for each call. Possible status or error codes are listed and explained. References are done in a consistent way using APA or IEEE.&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell></cells></criterion><criterion name="Application and code" sort_order="2"><cells><cell level_id="66912" cell_value="0.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="66907" cell_value="3.000000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;The application lacks in one or more of the following areas. It does not start or crashes. It does not fulfill the important requirements. It doesn't handle errors correctly. The code is a mess. It is hard to navigate. It is hard to understand. It is illogical. Separation of concerns is nowhere to be found or not respected. &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="66906" cell_value="6.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="66905" cell_value="9.000000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;The application fulfills the important requirements. Errors are handled and communicated to the outside world correctly. The code is easy to navigate. All code is useful and logical. The code is layered and respects separation of responsibilities. Classes have clear and few responsibilities. &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="66904" cell_value="12.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="66913" cell_value="15.000000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;The application is complete, fulfilling all requirements. The application is stable and robust. Errors are handled on the correct level and according to the standards of the used framework. Errors are communicated to the outside world in a useful way and using an accepted standard. The code is neat, the structure is easy to understand and navigate. The code is layered, respecting the separation of responsibilities. Classes and methods have clear and only one or a few responsibilities. The code structure and conventions follow the standards as dictated by the used frameworks. All code is useful, readable, logical and robust. Comments are useful and clarify parts that are hard to understand.&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell></cells></criterion><criterion name="Maintainability" sort_order="3"><cells><cell level_id="66912" cell_value="0.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="66907" cell_value="3.000000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;There is an incomplete README and/or dockerization. Or they don't work. There are not tests for the important functionality, or the tests do not work. &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="66906" cell_value="6.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="66905" cell_value="9.000000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;A README file adequately explains how to run the application and/or tests. The application can be fully started using docker. The README contains sample credentials to test the application with. Tests ensure that the most important requirements are complete and robust. &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="66904" cell_value="12.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="66913" cell_value="15.000000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;A proper README file is present, explaining adequately all the steps and prerequisites needed to develop for and/or run the application and tests. Each step is explained well to help the developer understand why each step is needed. The application is completely dockerized: everything can be started using one command. This includes the application and the database. Instructions how to run this command are also in the README file. The README contains sample credentials to test the application with. URLs, secrets, connectionstrings, etc., are configurable. Tests ensure that all requirements are both complete and robust. Test results are reported in the documentation and related back to the requirements. The tests are automated. All tests adhere to the coding standards.&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell></cells></criterion></criteria></criteria_group><criteria_group name="Advanced Tracks" sort_order="2"><level_set><levels><level name="Bad" sort_order="1" level_id="66916" /><level name="Insufficient" sort_order="2" level_id="66917" /><level name="Poor" sort_order="3" level_id="66918" /><level name="Sufficient" sort_order="4" level_id="66919" /><level name="Good" sort_order="5" level_id="66920" /><level name="Excellent" sort_order="6" level_id="66921" /></levels></level_set><criteria><criterion name="1. R &amp; A" sort_order="1"><cells><cell level_id="66916" cell_value="0.000000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;(did not do this track)&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="66917" cell_value="0.001000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;One or more of the following problems: The application can't be updated without going offline, no transactions are used in the application, there is no logging on several levels, there is no way to create reports for the logging, there is no monitoring system. The technical design or manual is lacking. &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="66918" cell_value="0.002000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="66919" cell_value="0.003000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;There is a mechanism to update the application without the application going offline. A monitoring system can react to possible problems. The application uses transactions to maintain consistency in the data. Logging is done on several levels. Users can create reports based on the logging. The technical designs describes all features and measures that were taken, and all configuration details. A manual provides information on how to use the logging and monitoring system. &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="66920" cell_value="0.004000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="66921" cell_value="0.005000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;The CI/CD includes a mechanism to update the application without the application going offline. There is a monitoring system that monitors all possible problems and that can be configured to warn admins about events. The application uses transactions to maintain consistency in the data. Logging is done on several levels. Users can create reports and graphs based on the logging using filters like date, userid, loglevel. The technical design describes all features and measures that were taken in detail. All configuration details are described. A manual provides information on how to use the logging and montoring system.&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell></cells></criterion><criterion name="2. ED" sort_order="11"><cells><cell level_id="66916" cell_value="0.000000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;(did not do this track)&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="66917" cell_value="0.001000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;One or more of the following problems: the data service(s) used are not valid for use in this track. The data is not used in the application or is not integrated in a useful way. There is no configuration interface. There is no signalling system. The application doesn't handle hickups in the external service well. The technical design is lacking. &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="66918" cell_value="0.002000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="66919" cell_value="0.003000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;The application connects to one or more external data services that have been approved to be valid for this track by the teacher. The application integrates this data in a useful way into the application. There is a configuration interface for the service. There is a signalling system to warn an admin about the service being offline. The application does not crash when the service is down. The technical designs describes all features and measures that were taken, and all configuration details. &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="66920" cell_value="0.004000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="66921" cell_value="0.005000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;The application connects to one or more external data services that have been approved to be valid for this track by the teacher. The application integrates this data in a logical and useful way into the application. There is a configuration interface that exposes all configuration details to an admin. There is a signalling system to warn an admin about events around the service. The application can handle latency or the service being offline, with fast and clear communication to the user. An automated test suite proves this. The technical design describes all features and measures that were taken in detail. All configuration details are described.&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell></cells></criterion><criterion name="3. QM &amp; D" sort_order="21"><cells><cell level_id="66916" cell_value="0.000000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;(did not do this track)&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="66917" cell_value="0.001000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;One or more of the following problems: there is no branch policy in place or it is lacking, there are no different environments, or parts of the environments are shared. The tests are not automated or fail. There is no automatic build or deployment. The technical design is lacking. &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="66918" cell_value="0.002000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="66919" cell_value="0.003000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;There are two or more environments at which the deployment is done, each having a totally separate stack. The deployment is automatic, including updating and deploying of the database. Automated API tests prove the API works. Each commit triggers build and deployment. The technical design describes all features and measures that were taken, and all configuration details. &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="66920" cell_value="0.004000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="66921" cell_value="0.005000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;There are two or more environments at which the deployment is done, each having a totally separate stack. The deployment is fully automated, including deployment, updates and data-conversion of the database. API tests cover the entire API and prove it works. The tests are idempotent and fully automated. Each commit to the repository triggers an automatic build, test, deployment and API tests after deployment. The technical design describes all features and measures that were taken in detail. All configuration details are described.&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell></cells></criterion><criterion name="4. Sec" sort_order="31"><cells><cell level_id="66916" cell_value="0.000000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;(did not do this track)&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="66917" cell_value="0.001000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;One or more of the following problems: no valid https, passwords are not hashed or no SSO used, sensitive data is not encrypted, no access control according to OWASP recommendations. The automatic process is lacking. The technical design is lacking. &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="66918" cell_value="0.002000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="66919" cell_value="0.003000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;The API is available via https. Passwords are hashed or an SSO solution is used. Sensitive data is encrypted. Access control is done following the recommendations of OWASP. One other recommendation of the OWASP has been followed. Automated tests prove the important measures. An automated process ensures that security is maintained. The technical design describes all features and measures that were taken, and all configuration details.&amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="66920" cell_value="0.004000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="66921" cell_value="0.005000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;The API is available via valid https on at least two different domains (production and acceptance). Passwords are hashed according to the latest OWASP recommendations, or an SSO solution is used. All sensitive data is encrypted. Hashing and encryption is environment specific. Access control is done following the recommendations of OWASP. One other recommendation of the OWASP has been followed. All measures are proven by automated tests. An automated process ensures that security is maintained by covering that changes are reviewed, tested and deployed. The technical design describes all features and measures that were taken in detail. All configuration details are described.&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell></cells></criterion><criterion name="Advanced track score" sort_order="41"><cells><cell level_id="66916" cell_value="0.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="66917" cell_value="3.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="66918" cell_value="6.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="66919" cell_value="9.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="66920" cell_value="12.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="66921" cell_value="15.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell></cells></criterion></criteria></criteria_group></criteria_groups><overall_level_set><overall_levels><overall_level name="Bad" sort_order="5" range_start_value="0.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level><overall_level name="Insufficient" sort_order="6" range_start_value="12.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level><overall_level name="Poor" sort_order="4" range_start_value="24.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level><overall_level name="Sufficient" sort_order="3" range_start_value="36.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level><overall_level name="Good" sort_order="1" range_start_value="48.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level><overall_level name="Excellent" sort_order="2" range_start_value="60.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level></overall_levels></overall_level_set></rubric><rubric id="3" resource_code="E3B84118-B59F-4D0C-847A-CA9AEC8F29C8-99547" name="DE assignment 1" type="1" scoring_method="2" display_levels_in_des_order="False" state="0" visibility="0" uses_overall_score="True" has_manual_alignment="False" score_visible_to_assessed_users="True" enabled_feedback_copy="False" usage_restrictions="Competency,ePortfolio"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><criteria_groups><criteria_group name="Criteria" sort_order="1"><level_set><levels><level name="None" sort_order="5" level_value="0.000000000" level_id="67131" /><level name="Insufficient" sort_order="6" level_value="2.000000000" level_id="67126" /><level name="Poor" sort_order="4" level_value="4.000000000" level_id="67125" /><level name="Sufficient" sort_order="3" level_value="6.000000000" level_id="67124" /><level name="Good" sort_order="1" level_value="8.000000000" level_id="67123" /><level name="Excellent" sort_order="2" level_value="10.000000000" level_id="67132" /></levels></level_set><criteria><criterion name="Idea concepts and problem definition" sort_order="1"><cells><cell level_id="67131" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67126" cell_value=""><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;You identified a problem but you focused on the solution instead of figuring out the underlying problem. The concepts are focused on one solution. &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67125" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67124" cell_value=""><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;You have correctly identified a problem and wrote it down in a concise and understandable manner. Your idea concepts are three different ideas and substantiated with visual elements (for example but not limited to: collaging, sketches, mock-ups etc). &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67123" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67132" cell_value=""><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;Your problem is well elaborated and the concepts are unique and visually appealing.&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell></cells></criterion><criterion name="Wireframes and requirements" sort_order="2"><cells><cell level_id="67131" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67126" cell_value=""><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;Your wireframes are poorly designed and unclear. They do not match the requirements and it is unclear why they are being created. &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67125" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67124" cell_value=""><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;Your wireframes have a visual hierarchy (for example but not limited to clear headings and sub-text, clear buttons etc.) and your requirements describe your system properly in MoSCoW. &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67123" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67132" cell_value=""><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;Your wireframes are extensive and match your requirements. All requirements have been elicited.&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell></cells></criterion><criterion name="User research methods" sort_order="3"><cells><cell level_id="67131" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67126" cell_value=""><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;Nonsensical research has been done. The methods do not match in any way &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67125" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67124" cell_value=""><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;Your research methods are clearly explained and you clarify how you carried out your research that you substantiate and justify with fitting sources. &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67123" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67132" cell_value=""><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;You have an extensive research which links with the problem stated, the requirements as well as the low-fi prototype.&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell></cells></criterion><criterion name="Presentation as a whole" sort_order="13"><cells><cell level_id="67131" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67126" cell_value=""><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;The pitch is of poor quality. It's not clear what the problem is and how you will resolve it. &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67125" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67124" cell_value=""><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;You have a standpoint on how to convince your user to use your product and your presentation matches the problem that you're describing. &amp;nbsp; &amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67123" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67132" cell_value=""><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;The pitch is perfect, we all want to buy your product. You are open to other suggestions and can defend and explain your own points of view.&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell></cells></criterion></criteria></criteria_group></criteria_groups><overall_level_set><overall_levels><overall_level name="None" sort_order="5" range_start_value="0.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level><overall_level name="Insufficient" sort_order="6" range_start_value="8.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level><overall_level name="Poor" sort_order="4" range_start_value="16.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level><overall_level name="Sufficient" sort_order="3" range_start_value="24.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level><overall_level name="Good" sort_order="1" range_start_value="32.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level><overall_level name="Excellent" sort_order="2" range_start_value="40.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level></overall_levels></overall_level_set></rubric><rubric id="4" resource_code="E3B84118-B59F-4D0C-847A-CA9AEC8F29C8-99548" name="DE assignment 2" type="1" scoring_method="2" display_levels_in_des_order="False" state="0" visibility="0" uses_overall_score="True" has_manual_alignment="False" score_visible_to_assessed_users="True" enabled_feedback_copy="False" usage_restrictions="Competency,ePortfolio"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><criteria_groups><criteria_group name="Criteria" sort_order="1"><level_set><levels><level name="None" sort_order="5" level_value="0.000000000" level_id="67151" /><level name="Insufficient" sort_order="6" level_value="4.000000000" level_id="67146" /><level name="Poor" sort_order="4" level_value="8.000000000" level_id="67145" /><level name="Sufficient" sort_order="3" level_value="12.000000000" level_id="67144" /><level name="Good" sort_order="1" level_value="16.000000000" level_id="67143" /><level name="Excellent" sort_order="2" level_value="20.000000000" level_id="67152" /></levels></level_set><criteria><criterion name="High fidelity prototype" sort_order="1"><cells><cell level_id="67151" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67146" cell_value=""><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;Your Figma prototype is working poorly (for example but not limited to; unclickable buttons, bad test cases, unconnected screens, etc.). You only visualized the most basic requirements&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67145" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67144" cell_value=""><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;Your Figma prototype is working and you have a visual hierarchy and aesthetics (for example but not limited to; the coloring matches, all your functionalities have a clear purpose etc.).&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67143" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67152" cell_value=""><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;You created a visually appealing prototype based upon your branding and research. Multiple bad weather cases are being implemented and the user receives feedback accordingly.&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell></cells></criterion><criterion name="Design choices" sort_order="2"><cells><cell level_id="67151" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67146" cell_value=""><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;Your brand and chosen research methods to back them up don't match up. It's unclear why you made certain choices.&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67145" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67144" cell_value=""><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;Nielsen and Norman heuristics are adequately applied - and your design choices for color, typography etc. have been justified using research methods (for example but not limited to; you make use of literature, prototyping, A/B testing etc. to back-up your choices).&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67143" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67152" cell_value=""><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;You created a fully formed brand identity and made good use of the design techniques shown in class. There is also a clear view on why you used which techniques.&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell></cells></criterion><criterion name="Testing report" sort_order="3"><cells><cell level_id="67151" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67146" cell_value=""><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;The UX testing methods you chose do not make sense or are implemented badly. It's not clear how or what you tested, what the process is in your testing phases or what you tried to figure out.&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67145" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67144" cell_value=""><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;You have made use of clear UX testing methods that are described step by step and provide new information on the user experience of your app.&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67143" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67152" cell_value=""><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;You made use of clear UX testing methods and gave a clear insight in how your prototype has changed based on the feedback.&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell></cells></criterion></criteria></criteria_group></criteria_groups><overall_level_set><overall_levels><overall_level name="None" sort_order="5" range_start_value="0.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level><overall_level name="Insufficient" sort_order="6" range_start_value="12.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level><overall_level name="Poor" sort_order="4" range_start_value="24.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level><overall_level name="Sufficient" sort_order="3" range_start_value="36.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level><overall_level name="Good" sort_order="1" range_start_value="48.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level><overall_level name="Excellent" sort_order="2" range_start_value="60.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level></overall_levels></overall_level_set></rubric><rubric id="5" resource_code="E3B84118-B59F-4D0C-847A-CA9AEC8F29C8-99549" name="HD assignment 1" type="1" scoring_method="2" display_levels_in_des_order="False" state="0" visibility="0" uses_overall_score="True" has_manual_alignment="False" score_visible_to_assessed_users="True" enabled_feedback_copy="False" usage_restrictions="Competency,ePortfolio"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><criteria_groups><criteria_group name="Criteria" sort_order="1"><level_set><levels><level name="None" sort_order="5" level_value="0.000000000" level_id="67169" /><level name="Insufficient" sort_order="6" level_value="4.000000000" level_id="67164" /><level name="Poor" sort_order="4" level_value="8.000000000" level_id="67163" /><level name="Sufficient" sort_order="3" level_value="12.000000000" level_id="67162" /><level name="Good" sort_order="1" level_value="16.000000000" level_id="67161" /><level name="Excellent" sort_order="2" level_value="20.000000000" level_id="67170" /></levels></level_set><criteria><criterion name="Framework selection" sort_order="1"><cells><cell level_id="67169" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67164" cell_value=""><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;The research document has one of the following problems. It contains errors or is incomplete. There is no systematic way of scoring the frameworks. The document is highly opiniated or bias.&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67163" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67162" cell_value=""><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;There is a well-written research document. Both generic criteria and criteria from the advanced track are used. Each framework has been scored in an systematic and understandable way. Decisions are justified. An overview shows the final scores. Referencing is done using APA or IEEE. All reasoning is comprehensive and logical.&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67161" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67170" cell_value=""><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;There is a thorough, well-written research document with cover, TOC, introduction and conclusion. Each framework has been described. All criteria and its weight are described, including the reasoning behind it. The criteria include personalised criteria that are applicable to the chosen assignment (at Design Essentials and for assignment 2). Each framework has been scored in a systematic and repeatable way. All decisions are justified and backed by sources, using a consistent way of referencing using APA or IEEE. An overview shows the final scores in a clear way. All text is well-written, informative, consistent, comprehensive, clear and logical.&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell></cells></criterion><criterion name="Prototyping and conclusi" sort_order="2"><cells><cell level_id="67169" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67164" cell_value=""><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;The research document has one of the following problems. It contains errors or is incomplete. The reflection is not systematic. The conclusion is not logical or based mainly on opinions or bias.&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67163" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67162" cell_value=""><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;There is a research document for the prototyping phase. The document describes the prototyping phase and reflects on the use of both frameworks. The reflection is systematic, clear and logical and based on own experiences. The conclusion is clear and logical, and in line with the reflections.&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67161" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67170" cell_value=""><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;There is a well-written research document for the prototyping phase. The document describes the prototyping phase and reflects on the use of both frameworks. The reflection is uniform for both frameworks, and based on own experiences. The reflection is systematic and uses the criteria from phase 1. A final conclusion has been drawn that is in line with the reflections. The conclusion does not introduce new information. All text is well-written, informative, consistent, comprehensive, clear and logical.&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell></cells></criterion></criteria></criteria_group></criteria_groups><overall_level_set><overall_levels><overall_level name="None" sort_order="5" range_start_value="0.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level><overall_level name="Insufficient" sort_order="6" range_start_value="8.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level><overall_level name="Poor" sort_order="4" range_start_value="16.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level><overall_level name="Sufficient" sort_order="3" range_start_value="24.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level><overall_level name="Good" sort_order="1" range_start_value="32.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level><overall_level name="Excellent" sort_order="2" range_start_value="40.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level></overall_levels></overall_level_set></rubric><rubric id="6" resource_code="E3B84118-B59F-4D0C-847A-CA9AEC8F29C8-99550" name="HD assignment 2" type="1" scoring_method="3" display_levels_in_des_order="False" state="0" visibility="0" uses_overall_score="True" has_manual_alignment="False" score_visible_to_assessed_users="True" enabled_feedback_copy="False" usage_restrictions="Competency,ePortfolio"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><criteria_groups><criteria_group name="Criteria" sort_order="1"><level_set><levels><level name="Bad" sort_order="1" level_id="67189" /><level name="Insufficient" sort_order="2" level_id="67188" /><level name="Poor" sort_order="3" level_id="67187" /><level name="Sufficient" sort_order="4" level_id="67186" /><level name="Good" sort_order="5" level_id="67185" /><level name="Excellent" sort_order="6" level_id="67190" /></levels></level_set><criteria><criterion name="Functional document" sort_order="1"><cells><cell level_id="67189" cell_value="0.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67188" cell_value="3.000000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;There is a functional document that doesn't clarify the important parts of the application. There are no wireframes or they are not explained.&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67187" cell_value="6.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67186" cell_value="9.000000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67185" cell_value="12.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67190" cell_value="15.000000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;There is a thorough and well-written functional document. All parts are clear, logical, useful, consistent, and complete. It contains the reason for this application and a list of prioritised requirements. The requirements are elaborated in detail and support a way to identify individual requirements. The design gives an overview of the application using wireframes and explanations, making clear how each screen works and the flow between screens through the application. The wireframes are linked to the requirements to show why certain parts are present in the wireframes. Parts that are harder to understand are explained in more detail. Diagrams are included to replace descriptive text and the text that is present is mostly to support the diagrams. Functional choices are explained. All contents and diagrams reflect the state of the implemented application. References are done in a consistent way using APA or IEEE.&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell></cells></criterion><criterion name="Application and code" sort_order="2"><cells><cell level_id="67189" cell_value="0.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67188" cell_value="6.000000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;The project has one of the following problems. There is an app that doesn't have enough functionality for the time available. The application crashes. Important functionality doesn't work correctly.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;OR&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;The code has one or more of the following problems. It is a mess. It is hard to navigate. It is hard to understand. It is illogical. Separation of concerns is nowhere to be found or not respected.&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67187" cell_value="12.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67186" cell_value="18.000000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67185" cell_value="24.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67190" cell_value="30.000000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;The application is complete and has enough functionality for the amount of time available. The application runs without crashes or technical errors. User or environment errors are handled correctly and the user is informed about how to solve the error. There is interaction with the backend API. There is native interaction. The code is neat, the structure is easy to understand and navigate. The code structure and conventions follow the standards as dictated by the used frameworks. All code is useful, readable, logical and robust. Comments are useful and clarify parts that are hard to understand. The code is layered, respecting the separation of responsibilities. Classes and methods have clear and only one or a few responsibilities. It is easy for a new developer to add new functionality. There are reusable and reused UI-components.&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell></cells></criterion><criterion name="Quality assurance" sort_order="3"><cells><cell level_id="67189" cell_value="0.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67188" cell_value="3.000000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;One or more of the following problems. The test don't cover the important components. There is no proof of actual testing. The static code analysis gives errors.&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67187" cell_value="6.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67186" cell_value="9.000000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67185" cell_value="12.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67190" cell_value="15.000000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text>&lt;p&gt;Tests prove the stability and completeness of all components of the app. There is a link between the tests and the requirements. Test reports show when the tests were executed and with what result. There are automatic tests. The project includes static code analysis to ensure code quality.&lt;/p&gt;</text></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell></cells></criterion></criteria></criteria_group></criteria_groups><overall_level_set><overall_levels><overall_level name="Bad" sort_order="5" range_start_value="0.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level><overall_level name="Insufficient" sort_order="6" range_start_value="12.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level><overall_level name="Poor" sort_order="4" range_start_value="24.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level><overall_level name="Sufficient" sort_order="3" range_start_value="36.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level><overall_level name="Good" sort_order="1" range_start_value="48.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level><overall_level name="Excellent" sort_order="2" range_start_value="60.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level></overall_levels></overall_level_set></rubric><rubric id="7" resource_code="E3B84118-B59F-4D0C-847A-CA9AEC8F29C8-99551" name="Project" type="1" scoring_method="3" display_levels_in_des_order="False" state="0" visibility="0" uses_overall_score="True" has_manual_alignment="False" score_visible_to_assessed_users="True" enabled_feedback_copy="False" usage_restrictions="Competency,ePortfolio"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><criteria_groups><criteria_group name="Criteria" sort_order="1"><level_set><levels><level name="None" sort_order="1" level_id="67551" /><level name="Insufficient" sort_order="2" level_id="67550" /><level name="Sufficient" sort_order="3" level_id="67549" /><level name="Good" sort_order="4" level_id="67548" /><level name="Excellent" sort_order="5" level_id="67556" /></levels></level_set><criteria><criterion name="Requirements" sort_order="1"><cells><cell level_id="67551" cell_value="0.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67550" cell_value="3.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67549" cell_value="6.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67548" cell_value="8.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67556" cell_value="10.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell></cells></criterion><criterion name="UX design" sort_order="2"><cells><cell level_id="67551" cell_value="0.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67550" cell_value="4.000000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67549" cell_value="8.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67548" cell_value="12.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67556" cell_value="15.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell></cells></criterion><criterion name="Architectural choices" sort_order="3"><cells><cell level_id="67551" cell_value="0.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67550" cell_value="4.000000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67549" cell_value="8.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67548" cell_value="12.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67556" cell_value="15.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell></cells></criterion><criterion name="Full stack system and tests" sort_order="13"><cells><cell level_id="67551" cell_value="0.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67550" cell_value="6.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67549" cell_value="11.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67548" cell_value="16.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67556" cell_value="20.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell></cells></criterion><criterion name="Maintainability" sort_order="23"><cells><cell level_id="67551" cell_value="0.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67550" cell_value="4.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67549" cell_value="8.000000000"><description text_type="text/html"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67548" cell_value="12.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67556" cell_value="15.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell></cells></criterion><criterion name="Project management" sort_order="33"><cells><cell level_id="67551" cell_value="0.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67550" cell_value="4.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67549" cell_value="8.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67548" cell_value="12.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67556" cell_value="15.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell></cells></criterion><criterion name="Client relations" sort_order="43"><cells><cell level_id="67551" cell_value="0.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67550" cell_value="3.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67549" cell_value="6.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67548" cell_value="8.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67556" cell_value="10.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell></cells></criterion></criteria></criteria_group></criteria_groups><overall_level_set><overall_levels><overall_level name="None" sort_order="5" range_start_value="0.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level><overall_level name="Insufficient" sort_order="4" range_start_value="35.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level><overall_level name="Sufficient" sort_order="3" range_start_value="55.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level><overall_level name="Good" sort_order="1" range_start_value="75.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level><overall_level name="Excellent" sort_order="2" range_start_value="95.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level></overall_levels></overall_level_set></rubric><rubric id="8" resource_code="E3B84118-B59F-4D0C-847A-CA9AEC8F29C8-99552" name="Untitled" type="1" scoring_method="2" display_levels_in_des_order="True" state="0" visibility="0" uses_overall_score="True" has_manual_alignment="False" score_visible_to_assessed_users="True" enabled_feedback_copy="False" usage_restrictions="Competency,ePortfolio"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><criteria_groups><criteria_group name="Criteria" sort_order="1"><level_set><levels><level name="Level 1" sort_order="4" level_value="1.000000000" level_id="67599" /><level name="Level 2" sort_order="3" level_value="2.000000000" level_id="67598" /><level name="Level 3" sort_order="2" level_value="3.000000000" level_id="67597" /><level name="Level 4" sort_order="1" level_value="4.000000000" level_id="67596" /></levels></level_set><criteria><criterion name="Criterion 1" sort_order="1"><cells><cell level_id="67599" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67598" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67597" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67596" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell></cells></criterion><criterion name="Criterion 2" sort_order="2"><cells><cell level_id="67599" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67598" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67597" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67596" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell></cells></criterion><criterion name="Criterion 3" sort_order="3"><cells><cell level_id="67599" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67598" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67597" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67596" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell></cells></criterion></criteria></criteria_group></criteria_groups><overall_level_set><overall_levels><overall_level name="Level 1" sort_order="4" range_start_value="0.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level><overall_level name="Level 2" sort_order="3" range_start_value="5.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level><overall_level name="Level 3" sort_order="2" range_start_value="8.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level><overall_level name="Level 4" sort_order="1" range_start_value="11.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level></overall_levels></overall_level_set></rubric><rubric id="9" resource_code="E3B84118-B59F-4D0C-847A-CA9AEC8F29C8-99553" name="Untitled" type="1" scoring_method="2" display_levels_in_des_order="True" state="0" visibility="0" uses_overall_score="True" has_manual_alignment="False" score_visible_to_assessed_users="True" enabled_feedback_copy="False" usage_restrictions="Competency,ePortfolio"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><criteria_groups><criteria_group name="Criteria" sort_order="1"><level_set><levels><level name="Level 1" sort_order="4" level_value="1.000000000" level_id="67607" /><level name="Level 2" sort_order="3" level_value="2.000000000" level_id="67606" /><level name="Level 3" sort_order="2" level_value="3.000000000" level_id="67605" /><level name="Level 4" sort_order="1" level_value="4.000000000" level_id="67604" /></levels></level_set><criteria><criterion name="Criterion 1" sort_order="1"><cells><cell level_id="67607" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67606" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67605" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67604" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell></cells></criterion><criterion name="Criterion 2" sort_order="2"><cells><cell level_id="67607" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67606" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67605" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67604" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell></cells></criterion><criterion name="Criterion 3" sort_order="3"><cells><cell level_id="67607" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67606" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67605" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell><cell level_id="67604" cell_value=""><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></cell></cells></criterion></criteria></criteria_group></criteria_groups><overall_level_set><overall_levels><overall_level name="Level 1" sort_order="4" range_start_value="0.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level><overall_level name="Level 2" sort_order="3" range_start_value="5.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level><overall_level name="Level 3" sort_order="2" range_start_value="8.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level><overall_level name="Level 4" sort_order="1" range_start_value="11.000000000"><description text_type="text"><text /></description><feedback text_type="text"><text /></feedback></overall_level></overall_levels></overall_level_set></rubric></rubrics>